Thomas Crowe

Greenville, SC

wcrowe@g.clemson.edu | 864-630-3512 | Thomas Crowe | LinkedIn | GitHub: https://github.com/wtcrowe4

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Programming enthusiast who excels at learning new languages and technologies. Agile problem solver with experience building efficient full-stack applications utilizing multiple data management solutions. Motivated and committed professional who will go above and beyond to ensure tasks and projects are completed correctly in a timely manner. A team player with the ability to create relationships built on trust and support with co-workers and clients alike.

EDUCATION

N.C. State University

Raleigh, NC

Software Development Certificate Program

2022

Courses: HTML, CSS, Javascript, UIUX, Express, React, PostgreSQL, SQL, Python, Flask, Cybersecurity, SCSS, Typescript, AWS

Clemson University

Clemson, SC

125 Credit Hours in Computer Science and Computer Engineering

2009-2012

SKILLS PROFILE

Development Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, Typescript, Node, Express, Python, Flask, Django, C#, .NET, MAUI,

Redux, React, Angular, Svelt, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub

Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, SQL

Security: Identity and Access Management, Multi-factor Authentication, Google Authentication

Deployment Tools: Heroku, AWS, Netlify, Azure

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Rest-rant | N.C. State

6/2022

A scalable full-stack application for restaurant ratings and reviews utilizing the MERN stack.

Grocery-List | Partner Project

• A creative MERN stack application for making personal grocery lists, enhanced by a recipe API, utilizing user registration and login with bcrypt and JWT, Nodemailer.

Sports Book | Independent Project

8/2022

A lightweight React application for real-time sports scores and odds utilizing an API to keep data up to date.

Crowe Realty | Independent Project

A responsive full-stack application designed for listing residential properties using Angular, C#, and SQL

Discord Clone | N.C. State

A full-stack mobile friendly application intended to resemble Discord, using Django and SQL.

MAUI Finance | Independent Project

3/2023-Present

A cross platform .NET MAUI mobile application to keep up with stock data using a financial API.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Arnold's Famous Hamburgers: Powdersville, SC

8/2016-Present

Manager

- Responsible for day-to-day operations, and ensuring every customer has a good experience.
- Exceptional customer service and conflict resolution skills with the ability to create great relationships
- Using creativity to implement new ways to increase profit and sales.
- Built strong interpersonal and adaptive skills from managing multiple locations when needed.
- Utilizing strong problem-solving skills in a fast paced, high-pressure environment.
- Occasional debugging and setup improvements for clover machines and software.

Outback Steakhouse: Easley, SC

5/2011-3/2016

Bartender

- - Used planning and organization skills to manage stock of alcohol.
 - Required to thrive in demanding and stressful situations while keeping a good attitude.
 - Networked with bar guests while ensuring great service and making sure other diners got drinks quickly.
 - Created strong relationships which developed many regular customers.
 - Cultivated the ability to find things in common with anyone who dined with us.